<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="States">States</string>
    <string name="Emergency">Emergency</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cross_river">CrossRiver</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="enugu_info">Enugu, nicknamed the “coal city” is the capital of Enugu state in South-Eastern Nigeria.
The city is popular for its cuisine, robust industries and of course, the local palm wine.
Despite this, there’s a lot many people don’t know about Enugu. But of course, it’s never too late to learn.

The name Enugu derived from two Igbo words, “Énú Ụ́gwụ́” means “top of the hill or mountain”.
The name obviously denotes the city’s geography naturally decorated with rolling hills and valleys.
The city was named after “Enugu Ngwo” under which coal was discovered.
Enugu inhabited majorly by the Nike subgroup of the Igbo people, “ndi Nike” in the Igbo language means “those with strength or power”.

Enugu city has a population of about 1 million people.
This is one of the lesser populated metropolises in Nigeria.
The city experiences two distinct seasons: the recurring rainy and dry season separated by the dusty Harmattan weather.
It has a mean temperature of 26.7°C making it one of the most habitable cities in Nigeria.
Travellers to the city are advised to visit this “British Developed City” during the dry season after the rains have subsided.</string>
    <string name="crossRiver_Info">Cross River State is a coastal state in South Eastern Nigeria, named after the Cross River, which passes through the state.
Located in the Niger Delta, Cross River State occupies 20,156 square kilometers.
It shares boundaries with Benue State to the north, Enugu and Abia States to the west,
to the east by Cameroon Republic and to the south by Akwa-Ibom and the Atlantic Ocean.

The state has an estimated population of about 2.89 million people (2006) who have a rich and unique cultural heritage.
Ejagham and Efik are major languages of this state,
but the Igbo tribe and language are also present in its western land borders.
Forty percent of the estimated population constitutes the active population that is engaged in various economic activities;
ranging from subsistence agriculture to urban commerce and transport business.

Cross River State belongs to tropical rainfall belt where rainfall is usually seasonal and at times very heavy.
Humid tropical climate of about 1300 3000mm rain fall and 30°C mean annual temperatures prevail over Cross River State,
except on the Obudu Plateau, where the climate is subtemperate, with temperatures of 15°C 23°C.</string>

    <string name="lagos_info">Lagos (Yoruba: Èkó) is a city in the Nigerian state of Lagos.
The city, with its adjoining conurbation, is the most populous in Nigeria, and the most populous on the African continent.
It is one of the fastest growing cities in the world, and also one of the most populous urban agglomerations.
Lagos is a major financial centre in Africa;
the megacity has the highest GDP, and also houses one of the largest and busiest ports on the continent.

Lagos, which means "lakes", was a name given to the settlement by the Portuguese.
The present-day Lagos state has a high percentage of Awori clan, who migrated to the area from Isheri along the Ogun river.
Throughout history, it was home to a number of warring ethnic groups who had settled in the area.

Average temperatures in Lagos vary very little.
Considering humidity, temperatures feel hot all year with a fair chance of precipitation about half of the year.
The area is less temperate than some — in the 14th percentile for pleasant weather — compared to tourist destinations worldwide.
Weeks with ideal weather are listed above.
If you’re looking for the very warmest time to visit Lagos, the hottest months are March, April,
and then February. See average monthly temperatures below.
The warmest time of year is generally mid March where highs are regularly around 93.3°F (34.1°C) with temperatures rarely dropping below 78.7°F (25.9°C) at night.</string>

    <string name="hospitals">Health Centers/Hospitals</string>
    <string name="police_stations">Police Stations</string>
    <string name="emergency_lines">Emergency Quick Response Lines</string>
    <string name="lagos">Lagos</string>
    <string name="enugu">Enugu</string>
    <string name="cross_river">Cross River</string>
    <string name="nondonHotel">Nondon Hotels</string>
    <string name="nikeLakeHotel">Nike Lake Hotel</string>
    <string name="oaklanHotel">Oakland Hotel</string>
    <string name="related">Related:</string>
    <string name="adigSuites">Adig Suites</string>
    <string name="robanHotels">Roban Hotels</string>
    <string name="gldenRoyale">Golden Royale</string>
    <string name="ceasarPlce">Ceasar\'s Palace Hotel</string>
    <string name="ibisHotel">Ibis Hotel</string>
    <string name="fourPoint">Four Point Hotel</string>
    <string name="sheratonHotel">Sheraton Hotel</string>
    <string name="mirageHotel">Mirage Hotel</string>
    <string name="moutySuites">Mounty Suites</string>
    <string name="quickResponse">www.npf.gov.ng/complaint/</string>
    <string name="policeStationsweb">www.npf.gov.ng</string>
    <string name="uriHospitals">www.finelib.com/hospitals-and-medical-centres</string>
</resources>
